I made a mistake, it went to 150 but it reached
450. Okay, okay, so Sachin ji, I would like to
come to you. Look at the Jaray stock, if you
look at its buying, it seems to be down at around 4.
Recently, the stock
gave a pullback from the November low, but back
in December, from 16th December, we are seeing that
perhaps selling started from there
and it seems to be going down breaking the point from where this pullback came. The
stock is trading around the multi-month low, so tell me whether there are any signs of recovery from here
or is
bearish sentiment building upwards. Look, it has
tested some good supports on the weekly charts. 1730 and 1740 were the levels.
After testing these levels, it slid from here and the upward momentum continued
here. So, these
seem to be the immediate supports to me. If you are
in a position of 1730, then you can stay with a stop loss on its blow,
but if in case  If
these levels of 1730 are broken
then the downside movement can possibly continue till 1650.
I think for
now hold the positions with a stop loss below 1730. If
any further
rebound is seen, there will be
possibilities of reaching around 1900 and 1950 on the upside.
But in case if the levels of 1730 are broken then there will be
possibilities of testing the levels of 1650, hence it would be
advisable to exit the position there.